I am old.
It's time to step down.
This position will go to Fixer Lunar.
I doubt
anyone will have a problem with that.
If there are any concerns, state them.
This is for chairpersons only.
Why have you brought Fixer Solar in?
Here's the issue.
The successor
to the position of Fixer Celestial,
I truly believe, um,
it is not for you to decide.
This is the tradition.
How dare you presume to speak about this!
Fixer Celestial,
we have discovered recently,
and I say this with the utmost respect,
that the murder of Ching He's Fixer
is connected to you.
So your daughter's appointment
to the position of Fixer Celestial
is now on hold.
Okay.
All of you here
have already discussed this in private,
haven't you?
Do you really imagine
that this issue is for me to determine?
I understand that you can't accept this.
Thackery Huang
will never be
the true master of Ching He.
You are.
Oh, Father.
You must take back the position
that belongs to you.
Only you
are qualified to be Fixer Celestial.
Make both sides of the law be afraid.
And make sure they respect you.
THE FIXERS
THE FIX
Is anyone home?
I'm back.
Ah.
Lord Guan, I'm sorry.
If I see a pine, with luck,
I'll leave you the cash.
All right? Thanks.
They said
it was a buy-one-get-one-free sale,
so I travel all that way,
and I only get one bag?
Oh, why do I do this to myself?
I don't know.
Hmm. Lights.
What are you doing in the dark?
Didn't you pray this morning?
Do you have a guilty conscience?
-Praying brings blessings and better luck.
-You better be right about that.
See?
You're sneaking around
just to take a look at your phone.
You're sure you don't have another woman?
You don't have to worry.
Nobody wants an old swamp eel.
You're my second, third, fourth,
and fifth woman.
-There's no escaping your clutches.
-Study your father.
So you don't end up like him.
That mouth of his. So smooth.
-On and on and on.
-Well, you chose him.
Hey, I didn't raise you
to talk back to me like that.
Uh, welcome.
Hey, a good dog stays out of the way.
Hey, buddy.
This is all yours.
Ta-da.
Oh, I'm sorry
about forcing you to take time off.
Consider this an apology. Huh?
Uh…
-Remember me?
-Pork floss or scallion?
-He's offering you a bun.
-Oh.
Scallion, of course. Love that scallion.
You're very kind. Thank you.
Hey, I gotta say,
this partner of yours is really weird.
Only weirdos can be my partner.
Oh, it is so hard to connect with you.
What's happening with the police?
Welcome.
Come with us to the station.
We need your assistance.
They have no evidence,
so they can't do anything to me.
I'm glad you're all right.
The boss asked about you.
Put it all together.
Okay.
I'm not going back.
I'm getting old, man.
I've earned enough money these last years.
You're not gonna leave me
with this old fossil.
Hey, I gotta say.
Having such a difficult partner
is hard work.
He's bashful.
-Look.
-Mm.
-He's got a sharp tongue but a soft heart.
-Oh yes, I know.
Sharp tongue, heart of the girl,
nostrils huge, and eyes like pearls.
-If anything comes up, call Ching He.
-Yeah.
-You're paying.
-Huh?
Uh, for these two, that's 40.
-This is a hundred.
-Buddy. Hey, buddy.
-No need to do that. It's all right.
-Hey. No, I…
No, no. No need.
-Hey, you're back.
-Yes, we're home.
-Here. Hey, give it to me.
-This backpack's so heavy. Here.
-Oh. Hey. What's in there?
-Thank you. Let me see your hands.
So Noods and Shadow, who reported that?
Hey. Just to get this out of the way.
I didn't do it.
Fixers Expunge and Annul
would have cleaned up the scene.
Logically, there'd be nothing to show.
Should we investigate?
No, I've already sent people to do that.
The request this time is delicate.
The client is Hsiu of San He.
He's the right-hand man
of the association leader Lin Wan-li.
Lin Wan-li is currently missing,
but a witness reported
they saw Hsiu's subordinates
kidnapping him.
Hsiu denies he was involved.
He suspects Lin Kuei-pin is behind it all.
Lin Wan-li, the leader of San He,
was kidnapped.
I heard.
Wasn't it Lin Wan-li's deputy, Hsiu,
who did it?
If all San He's members start brawling,
are you ready for your next move?
Do you mean his rival, Lin Kuei-pin?
Lin Wan-li is not young.
Word on the street is there are two people
gunning for his position.
One is Lin Wan-li's younger brother,
Lin Kuei-pin.
Ah, get in!
The other is Hsiu.
One of them is like a hawk.
The other, like a dove.
They've always been at odds.
Hey.
Don't run up here.
All your brothers are still down there.
Where's your sense of loyalty?
How are you gonna face boss Hsiu,
you coward?
-After Lin Wan-li went missing…
-Fuck!
…Ling Kuei-pin began making moves
on Hsiu's territory.
He's calling for him
to release his brother.
I can't imagine that this guy won't jump
at the chance to make a move.
The current mayor's so-called
"capital of happiness and excellence"
is now a haven for organized crime.
Journalists have a new headline.
Shall we help to push this along?
Tell your boss, Hsiu,
that every day he holds my brother,
I'll be here to pay my respects.
Lin Kuei-pin!
Have you gone insane?
Why are you causing trouble here?
-You know what you've done.
-You think my men kidnapped Lin Wan-li?
If you won't tell the truth,
you're going to cop the flak.
Right!
They are San He members, after all.
Hsiu doesn't want both sides
to destroy each other…
San He has the power it has…
…which is why
he especially commissioned Ching He
to help find Lin Wan-li.
This could also be proof
that Lin Wan-li's disappearance
has nothing to do with Hsiu.
I can't take this one.
No fixer has ever dared
to refuse a case assigned by Ching He.
You used to work for San He.
You know how they operate.
You're best placed for this job.
I still can't take it.
Find someone else.
Have you forgotten
the rules of the Fixers?
Don't worry. We'll deal with it.
Why won't you do it?
You got a grudge against San He?
Don't ask. It's part of my past.
Just like I don't ask
about your business either.
Get it?
TRUTH IS STRANGER THAN FICTION
All around, mountains and waters combine.
Let's see if you're that divine.
Divine, huh? Master of pen and gun.
You're the most cultured in all of San He.
Ah.
I, Chen Liang-chi,
was meant to hold a pen.
Now I carry a gun.
And so I… I will definitely
send my daughter abroad to study.
The world will be her oyster.
Nice, nice.
-Your turn, your turn.
-Okay, I'll go. Give it here.
And…
Water.
Combine.
Ooh.
Will you look at that?
Your two months of practice
beat my two years.
-Ah.
-You on Viagra?
Come on, this is nothing.
Give me another two months.
I could hit a fly, I bet you.
-Well, that is incredible.
-Uh-huh.
Okay, okay. In two years, we'll arrange
a fly-shooting contest for Boss Wan.
You'll quickly rise up the ranks.
Hail to the chief
who rises to power by killing insects.
Candlelight glows on an autumn night.
Autumn.
Rise to power by killing insects.
I'm Chief Fly. Hail to the Chief Fly.
NOTHING IS SO BEAUTIFUL AS SPRING
SPRING
Looking for me?
What have you been up to lately?
Being the youngest son
of a political dynasty
who obeys his father
and knows how to keep a very low profile.
What's with the attitude?
You can't talk to Dad like that.
You're scolding me.
I want you
at this year's ancestor worship ceremony.
All the major media outlets will be there.
You can learn how to handle these things
from your brother.
Spend time with him.
Watch and learn. You understand?
As his puppet?
You're a member of the Hsueh family.
-Stop all this idling, and--
-Oh, so I am a Hsueh?
You won't be embarrassed
if your other son's in public?
Just do what I tell you.
If you really don't wanna go,
then please don't.
Dad only did this
because he wants to fix things with you.
Whatever I do,
it's never good enough for him.
Don't let me drag you down.
Don't you want to win his approval?
Dad would always like you to help out.
I would too.
I need a guy I can really trust
to help me out.
Your read on people and situations
is always second to none.
You're a natural.
I want Dad to see that.
DADDY NOT HERE?
ARE YOU ALONE?
Sorry.
I was tidying up in the back.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Um, that will be 100.
-Hmm.
The bread's half price
because it's end of the day.
Thank you.
He's very well behaved.
Yes. Here.
Ah, you're back.
Hiya.
DADDY NOT HERE? ARE YOU ALONE?
THE WAY OF THREE HARMONIES
No one needs to know
I met with the police,
so please don't tell anyone.
Our identity is sensitive, after all.
I understand.
Has Lin Wan-li made any enemies lately?
He's getting close to retirement.
All he wants is peace.
He never wants conflict with anyone now.
A-wan had already made arrangements.
He knew he wasn't getting any younger.
He wrote up his will a little while ago.
Word on the street
is that Lin Wan-li's kidnapping this time
is connected to Hsiu and Lin Kuei-pin.
I don't believe it.
Pin's his younger brother,
and Hsiu was a close associate.
Yu.
I heard the cops were here.
How come you didn't tell me?
I didn't have time.
So, officer,
why have you come here?
A-pin, the police are here
to help find your brother.
What's your unit?
Who sent you here?
A-wan? A-wan, it's me.
What's that sound? Hello?
Put it on speaker.
A-wan?
In three days, get on the bus.
The ransom is one million dollars.
Only Lin Wan-li's wife can board the bus.
If we find out anyone's following her,
we'll kill him immediately.
Hey, can you let me--
Did I hear that right?
Ransom of one million bucks.
Shit.
That's a fucking insult.
We recommend you do nothing for now.
Leave it up to the police.
We'll look after this one.
It's a family concern.
-The police can stay out of it.
-A-pin.
This will only make things harder
for your brother.
He should go.
Come with me, officer.
HUNG HSING BAKERY
Well, that's weird.
Why'd he close up so early?
He hasn't put anything away.
HU TUNG-YU, FIXER SHADOW, AGE 43
STATUS: DECEASED
Agent Terra,
what brings you here to see me?
Some things can't be discussed
over the phone.
We've been friends a long time,
and there's something
I need to warn you about.
Are you here to talk about the rumors
circulating about Ching He
that we leaked to the police,
internal secrets,
that we're planning
to have our own fixers knocked off?
It's not just us who've heard this.
Our clients have heard it as well.
We had several clients
who wanted to commission us.
And in the last few days,
they all canceled.
Someone out there
is obviously rumor-mongering,
but that's no reason for us to worry.
If clients feel
they can't keep their information private,
they could turn on Ching He at any time.
Three make a tiger.
A lie told often enough becomes the truth.
Don't forget.
When some people lose something,
all they want then is to own it.
Sir, Tristan is achieving
huge approval ratings.
The position of mayor
is well within his reach.
All thanks to you, Madam Fan.
We're grateful to Yeh Yueh Tong
for helping this time.
It's you who gave us the chance
to prove that.
What Ching He does well,
Yeh Yueh Tong does equally.
And we can outshine them.
I heard that Ching He's
been having some trouble lately.
Thackeray Huang's
working methods will only harm Ching He.
To ensure that Ching He continues,
the temple needs a whole new leader.
It sounds as if you've got some ideas.
Ching He Temple
is the organization's backbone.
The old guard wants to maintain
a position of neutrality.
Those days are gone.
It needs to live in the light
and partly in shadow.
For the light side,
the Hsueh family is the most qualified.
For the shadow, let me handle it.
As long as we're in tune,
the world will be at our feet.
You want to take over Ching He.
I only want returned
what rightfully belongs to me.
Oh, I see.
How about you give me one week?
After that,
I will give you a satisfactory answer.
Here.
We used to play chess, you and I.
What do you say?
Would you like a game?
Maybe next time.
I still have some things to take care of.
You and I.
We'll be seeing each other presently.
It seems it's not just Fixer Terra.
Earth, Arcane, Cosmos,
and Eon are also worried.
Now management knows of it.
We have to sort this out fast.
Invite Hsiu here.
Say that our services
will be free of charge
in the hope that they might do something
for Ching He.
If you fail to take over Ching He,
and Ching He turns on you…
…then that's a considerable risk.
Sir, have you heard
that Ching He
has a set of classified files
that could upturn
the whole political order?
I've heard that.
It's the cornerstone
that's allowed Ching He
to remain neutral all this time.
These special files are definitely there.
They are known as the Primordial Files.
Agent Primordium is the most elite Fixer
in the history of Ching He.
They handle classified requests
of the utmost delicacy.
Only the successive heads of Ching He know
where they're hidden.
Except for Thackeray Huang.
He has no idea.
And yet, I do.
If you support me
in dealing with Thackeray Huang,
both sides of the law
will be under our control.
You'll never have
a more influential supporter.
This bridge
connects both sides of the city.
One side represents order and power.
The other side embodies ambition
and opportunity.
They're not in opposition.
They coexist.
THREE-IN-ONE COMBO, AMAZING VALUE
TWENTY MILLION DOLLARS ONLY
I don't know
if your husband ever told you what I do.
Before he died,
he bought a life insurance policy
from our company.
This is what he left
for you and your child.
We hope it helps at this difficult time.
He was like that.
Refused to tell me anything.
Never shared his burdens.
I don't want this.
I just want him back.
Uh… we're sorry for your loss.
I know that money isn't part
of an insurance payout.
Thanks anyway.
I'm very sorry.
It's my fault.
If I hadn't shot and injured him…
…he'd still be alive.
Hm, don't flatter yourself.
Fixers take risks.
It's all in the job description.
We've laid Shadow to rest.
The rest is down to Fixer Expunge
and the others.
Hmm.
Hey. I thought the cleaning was done now.
When a fixer dies,
their partner brings their body back.
Then Fixer Expunge erases all records
that link the agent to Ching He.
I wish they could erase memories.
Mm.
Hey, how's the San He case going?
You don't care about San He.
You're right, I don't care about San He,
but I do care about my partner.
Oh. Uh, I accidentally hurt my hand
during the mission.
It'll get better soon, I'm sure.
Lin Kuei-pin's got Hsiu in his sights.
I'd say he's going to act
before the cash is handed over.
This current gang war
highlights the mayor's total incompetence.
The city of happiness
is now a city of gangsters.
Mayor, come out. We deserve an apology.
Go fuck yourself, Lin Kuei-pin.
TRAITOR
Don't neglect your duties
in the twilight of your term.
Continue to safeguard
the safety of your constituents.
Next stop,
Nanjing and Longjiang intersection.
I said wear a disguise,
not that we're catching trout.
A disguise is all about the detail.
As the saying goes,
Grand Duke Jiang fishes for crooks,
and the willing take the line.
What about you
wearing sunglasses at night?
Can you even see anything?
You again.
What's the deal now?
Is Yeh Yueh Tong
poaching all the temple's cases?
Our target is the same. Lin Wan-li.
It's not about Yeh Yueh Tong.
And tell me, are you fine?
Us working together?
-I'm okay.
-Who cares?
-Hello.
-Did you bring money?
I'm gonna get it from you now.
Where are you?
At the next stop,
toss the money out the back door.
Don't get off the bus.
If you miss the stop,
your husband will die.
Stop running, motherfucker.
Don't chase 'em.
I placed a tracker in there.
-Hey, we did it! We did it.
-What?
-Got the million dollars.
-You got the money.
Where's the money? Let me see.
Good thing I'm a fast runner,
or I could've got killed.
Take this roast duck
and pay your respects
to the God of Wealth.
Go on.
Dun, da, da, da, da!
God of Wealth, it's time to eat.
Why are you teasing me like this?
I've already seen your face.
You're joking. You can see my face?
Well, I can see your asshole.
Nice.
Your hair's dyed a kind of straw color.
Am I right?
What?
-Hey, he saw me, he saw me!
-What's up, huh?
-What are you saying?
-He saw me. Saw my face.
He saw you?
I told you not to use a garbage bag.
Have you kidnapped anyone before?
Did you really only ask
for one million dollars?
Do you think I'm that cheap… or San He?
-Huh?
-San He?
-What's this San He thing?
-How should I know?
-San He. San He, what is that?
-I'm Lin Wan-li.
You got a phone, right?
-Who's Lin Wan-li?
-Google it.
Hey.
-Well, is he? Is it him?
-Yes. Yes.
-Fuck!
-Stop. Stop, hey.
Of all the people we could kidnap,
why did we kidnap the San He guy?
Just shut up for a second.
I'll figure it out.
This is how we've always done it.
You're the muscle, I'm the brains.
-Okay?
-I'm hungry.
You get me a good feed,
I won't rat you out.
He says he's hungry. What should we do?
Sir, have a duck leg.
Okay.
What's the deal with you guys?
How'd you wind up
with the kidnap plan, huh?
We lost all our money playing poker.
Now we're in debt.
If we don't pay,
we'll lose the rest of our fingers.
How long have you two known each other?
We've hung out since we were kids.
-Uh-huh.
-We're good friends.
Ah.
Uh, looking at you two,
I'm reminded of two young men
who used to follow me.
They were a lot like you two.
They were a lot smarter than you.
They were cunning.
Huh?
In my whole life, I've never met two guys
as thick as you are.
He's right, you are.
Uh… when I think of the days
when they would follow me around,
they were the best days of my life.
Hmm.
Did you only speak to my wife?
What about the other gang members?
-Did you?
-Uh, no.
Tomorrow, I'll leave the mountain,
and I'll tell them I staged everything.
And that way, you'll be fine.
You can go pay off your gambling debts.
Once that's settled,
you work for me, all right?
-Really? Boss!
-Hey.
Hey, call him "boss." Call him "boss."
-Boss.
Ah…
Uh, reporting in, boss.
Nature calls.
-I'm going for a piss now.
-Yeah.
-Go on, go.
-Okay.
Uh-huh.
-You sit.
-All right.
Here.
What's that?
Am I being rescued?
Hmm?
Or am I being assassinated?
Boss Wan, we're just here to see you off.
A-pin?
That coward.
He should kill me himself,
but he doesn't have the guts.
I'm sorry.
Sharing this last meal,
it was a joy.
Boss Wan-li,
I'm very sorry.
Lin Wan-li.
Who would have thought?
You and I meeting again after so long.
Hang in there. Boss Wan will be here soon.
Hang in there. It'll be fine.
Just hang in there. Do you hear me?
You'll be fine.
They are not coming. Just go.
Yeah.
Hello, Fixer Fortune.
What's going on?
You remember the rule I told you?
When a fixer dies…
their partner has to collect the body.